Contact

sharmasachin95880@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sachin-sharma-99b577209 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Excel
Education
Computer Science

Sachin Sharma

5# coder in python ||3#Coder in C at HACKERRANK ||B .Tech (C.S.E) || Full STACK Web Developer (Free to Contact)
Agra

Summary

Experienced Business Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the e-learning industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Computer Science, Microsoft Access, English, and HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT NODE.JS MANGODB.MYSQL PYTHON DJStrong education professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from Bundelkhand University.

Experience

PrepBytes

6 months

Campus Business Manager: prepBytes August 2021 - Present (6 months)

Campus Business Manager August 2021 - Present (6 months)

Education

Bundelkhand University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (December 2020 - June 2024)